<?xml version="1.0"?>
<inspiringPersons>
    <inspiringPerson>
        <name>John Resig</name>
        <image>jeresig-full-profile-2013.jpg</image>
        <dateOfBirth>
            <year>1984</year>
            <month>5</month>
            <day>8</day>
        </dateOfBirth>
        <CV>American software engineer. Writer of jQuery. The first version was released in 2006.</CV>
        <citations>
            <citation>Write code every day</citation>
        </citations>
    </inspiringPerson>
    <inspiringPerson>
        <name>Alan Turing</name>
        <image>Alan_Turing_photo.jpg</image>
        <dateOfBirth>
            <year>1912</year>
            <month>6</month>
            <day>23</day>
        </dateOfBirth>
        <dateOfDeath>
            <year>1954</year>
            <month>6</month>
            <day>7</day>
        </dateOfDeath>
        <CV>British mathematician, logician, cryptanalyst, philosopher, pioneering computer scientist, mathematical biologist, and marathon and ultra distance runner. Turing is widely considered to be the father of theoretical computer science and artificial intelligence.</CV>
        <citations>
            <citation>We can only see a short distance ahead, but we can see plenty there that needs to be done.</citation>
            <citation>A computer would deserve to be called intelligent if it could deceive a human into believing that it was human.</citation>
            <citation>I believe that at the end of the century the use of words and general educated opinion will have altered so much that one will be able to speak of machines thinking without expecting to be contradicted.</citation>
        </citations>
    </inspiringPerson>
    <inspiringPerson>
        <name>Bjarne Stroustrup</name>
        <image>BjarneStroustrup.jpg</image>
        <dateOfBirth>
            <year>1950</year>
            <month>12</month>
            <day>30</day>
        </dateOfBirth>
        <CV>Danish computer scientist, most notable for the creation and development of the widely used C++ programming language (~1983).</CV>
        <citations>
            <citation>An organization that treats its programmers as morons will soon have programmers that are willing and able to act like morons only.</citation>
        </citations>
    </inspiringPerson>
    <inspiringPerson>
        <name>William Henry "Bill" Gates III</name>
        <image>Bill gates.jpg</image>
        <dateOfBirth>
            <year>1955</year>
            <month>10</month>
            <day>28</day>
        </dateOfBirth>
        <dateOfDeath>
            <year>2014</year>
            <month>11</month>
            <day>5</day>
        </dateOfDeath>
        <CV>American business magnate, philanthropist, investor, computer programmer, and inventor. Founder of Microsoft.</CV>
        <citations>
            <citation>If you can't make it good, at least make it look good.</citation>
            <citation>Your most unhappy customers are your greatest source of learning.</citation>
            <citation>Software is a great combination between artistry and engineering.</citation>
        </citations>
    </inspiringPerson>
</inspiringPersons>